let theQueensGambitQuestions = [
	{
		question: "About how many households have watched the series in its entirety?", 
		choiceA: "45 million",
		choiceB: "57 million",
		choiceC: "62 million",
		choiceD: "80 million",
		correctAnswer: "62 million"
	},
  {
		question: "Beth struggles to become a Grandmaster in chess..", 
		choiceA: "from the age of 7 to 20",
		choiceB: "from the age of 10 to 29",
		choiceC: "from the age of 8 to 22",
		choiceD: "from the age of 9 to 25",
		correctAnswer: "from the age of 8 to 22"
	},
  {
		question: "Though the show was set in the 1960s, when were women actually allowed to compete in the World Chess Championship?", 
		choiceA: "1950s",
		choiceB: "1970s",
		choiceC: "1980s",
		choiceD: "1970s",
		correctAnswer:  "1980s"
	},
  {
		question: "The miniseries is based on the 1983 novel of the same name by...", 
		choiceA: "Walter Tevis", 
		choiceB: "Katherine Neville",
		choiceC: "Stefan Ziger",
		choiceD: "Brad Pitt",
		correctAnswer: "Walter Tevis"
	},
  {
		question: "Which behavior do we see in Beth that is realistic of many chess players?", 
		choiceA: "Visualizing moves on the floor",
		choiceB: "Visualizing moves on the ceiling", 
		choiceC: "Visualizing moves on her palm", 
		choiceD: "Visualizing moves on her dreams",
		correctAnswer: "Visualizing moves on the ceiling"
	},
  {
		question: "The Queen's Gambit is a(n)...", 
		choiceA: "Canadian TV series by Netflix",
		choiceB: "UK TV series by Netflix", 
		choiceC: "American TV series by Netflix",
		choiceD: "Spanish TV series by Netflix",
		correctAnswer: "American TV series by Netflix",
	},
  {
		question: "Which chess champion may you recognize from also being an actor in five Harry Potter movies?", 
		choiceA: "Harry Beltik", 
		choiceB: "Vasily Borgov",
		choiceC: "Benny Watts", 
		choiceD: "Harry Potter",
		correctAnswer: "Harry Beltik"
	},
  {
		question: 'Complete the quote: \
â€œMen are gonna come along and wanna teach you things...', 
		choiceA: "Kick them back as hard as you can",
		choiceB: "Show them what you've got",
		choiceC: "Doesn't make them any smarter",
		choiceD: "Don't listen to them",
		correctAnswer: "Doesn't make them any smarter"
	},
  {
		question: "Which player scares Beth most?", 
		choiceA: "The Chinese",
		choiceB: "The Russian",
		choiceC: "The German",
		choiceD: "The Spanish", 
		correctAnswer:  "The Russian"
	},
  {
		question: "What do chess experts think of the show overall?", 
		choiceA: "They say it's unrealistic",
		choiceB: "They say it's very believable", 
		choiceC: "They say only a few parts of the show are accurate",
		choiceD: "They say it's very bad",
		correctAnswer: "They say it's very believable"
	},
];